Welcome back to my series where I
recreate Ben and Jerry's flavors, but
lower in calories and [music] higher in
protein. This is chocolatecovered
strawberry. Let me show you how to make
it. We're starting off with one
strawberry protein shake. You can use a
pre-made one. I like the ones from Nuri,
or you can make your own with strawberry
protein powder and some milk. And then
some extra sweetener, a little pinch of
salt, and a/4 teaspoon of zantham gum.
You can just blend that up. I like to
use an immersion blender. Throw it in
the freezer for at least 16 hours,
ideally 24. Then take it out, run it
under hot water for 30 seconds to a
minute, and then spin it in your creamy
on the light ice cream setting. Once
that's done, it should come out a little
bit powdery. If it's super powdery and
not melting on the sides at all, respin.
But if you see the ice cream melting on
the sides a little bit, it is time for
the mixing cycle. So, we'll haul out a
hole in the center and fill it with our
mixins. I'm using some low sugar
strawberry jam and then my chocolate
chip hat. Full recipe and instructions
will be down below in the caption. But
after that mixing cycle, you are good to
go. If you like the combination of
strawberry and chocolate, this is the
flavor for you. So much better than that
for me.